so let's do a quiz on the relative
merits of processor performance power
weight and cost we will have several
processor models with the relative
performance expected battery life wave
of the overall computer and the cost of
the processor the question for you is
which one of these will be the worst for
laptops the first model is the Crowe
Liam has very little performance very
long battery life extremely light and
they're cheap the next model is the
slogan it has much more performance half
the battery life however it's still very
light but it's four times as heavy as
the CRO Liam and about three times more
expensive then we have our lab team
processor it has twice the performance
of the slogan five hours of battery life
it's twice as heavy as the slogan costs
about $100 then we have the fast team
which has more performance significantly
less battery life however it's about one
pound in weight cost $200 for the
processor and then we have the Hatim
adds more performance fifteen-minute
battery life three pounds and 500
dollars and the bernam processor doubles
the performance of the Hatim it's
battery lasts two minutes it's 20 pounds
in weight and cost five thousand dollars
so which one of these would you least
want in your laptop